(Sheldon:)Bongo solo.
Stop. Stop it. Stop. Stop.
(Leonard:)Stop it.
- What the hell?
- Oh, hi, Penny, guess what?
(Leonard:)Sheldon got bongos.
- Why did you get bongos?
- Richard Feynman played the bongos.
l thought l'd try.
(Leonard:)Feynman was a famous physicist.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
l don't care if Richard Feynman was a
purple leprechaun who lived in my butt.
(Sheldon:)Penny meant
If he were a purple leprechaun
(Sheldon:)Penny forgot to use the subjunctive
(Leonard:)Sheldon, go to bed.
You have work in the morning.
(Sheldon:)Maybe, maybe not. Maybe tomorrow
l start a bongo band and tour the world.
No, hang on. Roommate Agreement.
(Leonard:)No hootenannies, sing-a-longs,
or barbershop quartets after 10 p.m.